<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Stan Yuzu</title>
    <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Stan Yuzu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NMB member rankings April 2023 edition</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2023-05-08-nmb-member-rankings-april-2023-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2023-05-08-nmb-member-rankings-april-2023-edition/</guid>
      <description>Intro This is the fifth time we have asked NMB fans from all around the world at the NMB discord server to submit their NMB member rankings. Thanks to everyone who did! We dropped quite a few voters again (44 compared to 51 in October and 54 last year!), NMB is clearly flopping! It is nevertheless still a good number and gives the result enough relevancy! The results saw some</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even more definitive 17th gen ranking</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2023-04-09-even-more-definitive-17th-gen-ranking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2023-04-09-even-more-definitive-17th-gen-ranking/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the second edition of 17th gen ranking! We thought the first one was kinda fun so why not do it again. We asked around everywhere, and in the end managed to get 40 votes, smashing the previous record of 15 votes! Thank you everyone! A comparison is made throughout with the previous, October edition of these member rankings (in the table below, they are the smaller numbers in</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NMB 28th single senbatsu predictions</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-12-14-nmb-28th-single-senbatsu-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-12-14-nmb-28th-single-senbatsu-predictions/</guid>
      <description>Just like last year, I’m offering some thoughts on what the senbatsu for the next single —- hopefully coming soon! —- might look like. It feels arguably harder this time, since it’s been about a year since management chose a senbatsu, and the current senbatsu includes members we do not really know how they feel about. There is also an entirely new generation (and likely two!) of girls to select from, while graduations slowed down significantly in 2022, mostly not affecting the pool of potential senbatsu candidates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUBKA September interview translation</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-11-11-bubka-september-interview-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-11-11-bubka-september-interview-translation/</guid>
      <description>B = BUBKA, Y = Yuzuha
Money Management B: You entered the group when you were 12 and now you are already at the end of your teens!
Y: I turn 20 in January.
B: You&amp;rsquo;ve probably done a lot of gravure with the theme of &amp;ldquo;between a girl and a woman&amp;rdquo;. Have you recently been asked more for ennuyé, graceful, stoic expressions?
Y: I have, sometimes, but I personally think that what my fans enjoy the most is the naturally smiley me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NMB member rankings October 2022 edition</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-11-10-nmb-member-rankings-october-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-11-10-nmb-member-rankings-october-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Intro This is the fourth time we have asked NMB fans from all around the world at the NMB discord server to submit their NMB member rankings. Thanks to everyone who did! We had slightly fewer voters this time (51 compared to 54 in April), but also stricter checks in place. At any rate, it is nice to see people still haven’t got tired</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some stats</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-11-02-some-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-11-02-some-stats/</guid>
      <description>There were recently two “popularity contests” that caught my attention. The first one was the project ran by NMB official Twitter, where all members performed a confession scene. The second one was an internet vote, which was irrelevant enough and employed decent security measures against not allowing one person to vote more than once (and excluding votes from foreign countries completely), that it produced results that align quite well with other data we have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>17th gen definitive ranking</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-10-09-17th-gen-definitive-ranking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-10-09-17th-gen-definitive-ranking/</guid>
      <description>One night, talking to my dear friends, I came up with the random idea to make a quick ranking of 17th gen girls. As a reward for that foolishness, I was harassed by them to use my precious free time to produce a report on the State of 17th generation about half a year after their famous debut.
I aggregated the votes they picked up god knows where, someone please check they are all even real, and produced the final result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuzu&#39;s photobook</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-08-06-yuzu-s-pb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-08-06-yuzu-s-pb/</guid>
      <description>On June 29 the crowning achievement of Yuzu&amp;rsquo;s 15 month long gravure career saw the light of the day, as her first photobook Utsukushī Kajitsu [Beautiful Fruit &amp;mdash; because yuzu is a fruit and Yuzu is beautiful&amp;hellip; I guess] was released. An achievement that would have sounded ridiculous before April 2021, but which became purely a matter of time after Yuzu&amp;rsquo;s successful gravure debut. It had been also obvious that the publisher would be Kōdansha, the company behind (among others) Young Magazine, the magazine which has been pushing Yuzu a lot and given her a lot of opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akarin&#39;s YT series stats</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-07-05-akarin-s-yt-series-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-07-05-akarin-s-yt-series-stats/</guid>
      <description>The video series hosted by a former first generation member Yoshida Akari has arrived to its finish. It was not without generating some heated discussions among fans throughout, but this article stays away from all of that and just looks at how the respective videos fared. For better or worse, the numbers are largely incomparable to each other, but it is also an useful exercise to show why! The main</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EX Taishū April interview translation (with Tanaka Miku)</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-04-17-ex-taishu-april-interview-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-04-17-ex-taishu-april-interview-translation/</guid>
      <description>E = EX Taishū, Y = Yuzuha, M = Miku The two girls who you can see literally every day on the shelves of bookstores and conbinis finally met! They had met at handshake events and talked over social media, but this was the first time they had a proper conversation. Talking their respective gravure, the confidence they gained through it, the promise of</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NMB member rankings April 2022 edition</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-04-12-nmb-member-rankings-april-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-04-12-nmb-member-rankings-april-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Intro This is the third time we have asked NMB fans from all around the world at the NMB discord server to submit their NMB member rankings. This time it was indeed a sort of an organized venture. (And that was only possible thanks to everyone who enjoyed the previous editions!) We managed to have even more voters this time (54 compared to 48 in October), which I had honestly not expected, considering how things had been going with NMB!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entame Web interview translation</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-03-21-entame-web-interview-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-03-21-entame-web-interview-translation/</guid>
      <description>I bring you a translation of a series of articles that kinda randomly appeared at the Entame news website. I found it interesting, because it puts Yuzu&amp;rsquo;s achievements in perspective and also contains some new small pieces of info which fill in some blank spots about her gravure debut and senbatsu debut.
Conquering every magazine&amp;rsquo;s gravure with her strong impact, NMB48&amp;rsquo;s Hongō Yuzuha &amp;mdash; The true face of a hard worker who was once almost buried for 6 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gekkan Entame January interview translation (with Rei)</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-01-31-gekkan-entame-january-interview-translation-with-rei/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-01-31-gekkan-entame-january-interview-translation-with-rei/</guid>
      <description>E = Entame, R = Rei, Y = Yuzuha
I want to turn fans&amp;rsquo; uneasiness into easiness E: Jōnishi-san was selected as the centre of NMB&amp;rsquo;s 26th single to be released in February and Hongō-san entered senbatsu for the first time.
R: Being selected as the centre was a dream I had held for a long time. My first reaction was &amp;ldquo;It cannot be!&amp;rdquo;; I have often been told that I am not a centre material, but the fact that I have managed to turn that dream into reality will hopefully make other members also believe that when they already managed to enter the group, they can for sure aim to be the centre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuzu in 2021</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-01-09-yuzu-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2022-01-09-yuzu-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Time flies so fast in the idol world that I might have completely forgot something important happening&amp;hellip; but hopefully this recap will be able to give a good general overview of Yuzu&amp;rsquo;s 2021 anyway. It was a year in which Yuzu became the biggest gravure star of 48G, almost tripled the number of her Twitter and Instagram followers, became a top 20 member in all 48G in Twitter and Instagram engagement numbers, and shoot up from a mid-tier NMB member to a senbatsu level member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUBKA December interview translation</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-12-28-bubka-december-interview-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-12-28-bubka-december-interview-translation/</guid>
      <description>B = BUBKA, Y = Yuzuha B: To Hongō-san, 2021 brought a dramatic change, didn&amp;rsquo;t it. Y: Yeah, I am still astonished. B: Could you have imagined something like this happening a year ago? Y: Nah, I don&amp;rsquo;t think so, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t even thought I would be doing gravure in the first place, so it all feels like a dream. B:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YNN 24H Line Distribution</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-12-26-ynn-24h-line-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-12-26-ynn-24h-line-distribution/</guid>
      <description>This is a very approximate YNN 24H appearance time ranking, based on a post in this matome, including Kani Game, not including the second Niconico commentary stream, and with several opinionated fixes:
In Kani Game I counted roughly each member’s time before their elimination (so Misaki would get 2 hours while Momone 10 minutes).
I went by the times mentioned in the matome post, which of course does not take breaks into consideration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Hongo Yuzuha?</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-12-17-who-is-hongo-yuzuha/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-12-17-who-is-hongo-yuzuha/</guid>
      <description>That is the title of an interesting article that was published yesterday (December 17) in the web magazine Daily Shincho, tracking Yuzuha&amp;rsquo;s rise to stardom through her still nascent, yet already massively successful gravure career &amp;mdash; and the article will hopefully convince you those are not pompous words!
グラビアでことし大ブレイクし、異例のヤンマガ2週表紙にもなったNMB48の本郷柚巴さん。その魅力についての記事を書きました。https://t.co/DsNkFlEjbm#NMB48 pic.twitter.com/bhRsuHxOD7
&amp;mdash; 徳重龍徳（インタビュアー、グラビア評論家）@ちいかわ好き、ホークスファン (@tatsunoritoku) December 17, 2021 Getting her big break after gravure debut, already being called the &amp;ldquo;New Generation Gravure Queen&amp;rdquo; The one who is currently getting her break and being lauded as the Next Generation Variety Queen is Shibuya Nagisa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Hits Kayosai senbatsu in numbers</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-11-16-best-hits-kayosai-senbatsu-in-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-11-16-best-hits-kayosai-senbatsu-in-numbers/</guid>
      <description>In this short post I look back on the recent NMB performance Best Hits Kayosai - from the perspective of Twitter and Instagram performance, because that’s we are about here (and because I was asked to do it)!
I looked at three indicators. All of the members posted on Twitter and Instagram after the performance. I compiled the number of likes (plus retweets) of these posts (if anyone posted more, I picked their best performing post).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NMB 26th single senbatsu predictions</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-10-20-nmb-26th-single-senbatsu-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-10-20-nmb-26th-single-senbatsu-predictions/</guid>
      <description>The announcement of NMB’s 26th single is imminent and it is therefore time for the most fun of activities an idol fan can enjoy — senbatsu predictions!
In this article, I try to look at all the members who I feel have at least some chance of entering senbatsu. I operate with the assumption that the senbatsu will have 16 members. It might always be more (after all, my final analysis would prefer an 18 member senbatsu), although with the current number of members it doesn’t seem necessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NMB member rankings October edition</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-10-05-nmb-member-rankings-october-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-10-05-nmb-member-rankings-october-edition/</guid>
      <description>Intro This is the second time we have asked NMB fans from all around the world at the NMB discord server to submit their NMB member rankings. The first time was at the beginning of April. It was completely unorganized and the whole “project” happened only because I had the silly idea of collecting all the rankings everyone had unsuspectingly posted. Back then, there were in total 16 entries - and I now also used the results of the April edition for an interesting comparison with the current October one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FLASH September interview translation (with Wakapon)</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-09-10-flash-september-interview-translation-with-wakapon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-09-10-flash-september-interview-translation-with-wakapon/</guid>
      <description>F = FLASH, W = Wakapon, Y = Yuzuha
F: Even though you two had been doing a lot of gravure, today&amp;rsquo;s pair shoot was the first time for you, which is kind of surprising.
Y: We had had surprisingly few interactions until now, so to see Wakapon could do such expressions allowed me to discover a new side of her and that was a lot of fun.
W: I enjoyed it as well, just singing together and doing the shoot and so on all in high spirits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUBKA September interview translation (with Rei)</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-09-02-bubka-september-interview-translation-with-rei/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-09-02-bubka-september-interview-translation-with-rei/</guid>
      <description>B = BUBKA, Y = Yuzuha, R = Rei
B: Today you had the chance to wear the historical clothes that Yamamoto Sayaka and Shiroma Miru had worn.
R+Y: We&amp;rsquo;re glad!
B: In a previous (August) issue, when you two together with Shiroma-san were on the cover, Shiroma-san was saying: &amp;ldquo;They have to wear that!&amp;rdquo; So before her graduation, we held a succession ceremony like that.
R: I had the red one [they are here referring to the feather boa that Sayanee, Miru (and redacted Suuchan) had worn before - along with the black mizugi]; I did admire it and wanted to wear it at some point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUBKA July interview translation (with Miru and Rei)</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-06-30-bubka-july-interview-translation-with-miru-and-rei/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-06-30-bubka-july-interview-translation-with-miru-and-rei/</guid>
      <description>B = BUBKA, M = Miru, Y = Yuzuha, R = Rei
B: The BUBKA release that featured Hongo-san&amp;rsquo;s gravure was well-received, with a flood of preorders coming in and news about bookstores selling out coming in one after another.
M: Wooow!
Y: Thank you!
M: I had wondered since a long time ago when Yuzu&amp;rsquo;s boobs would see the light of day.
Y: haha
M: I would be like touching you when we were changing clothes in the dressing room, right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUBKA May interview translation</title>
      <link>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-04-27-bubka-may-interview-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stanyuzu.netlify.app/post/2021-04-27-bubka-may-interview-translation/</guid>
      <description>B = BUBKA, Y = Yuzuha B: Hongo-san&amp;rsquo;s gravure was something like a long-awaited wish. We actually made the offer some time ago already. Y: Oh! Thank you very much! B: And the words &amp;ldquo;long-awaited&amp;rdquo; were never as appropriate as this time. Y: Haha no way. B: At the end of the last year, Mizuta Shiori chose top 5 members whose gravure she wanted to see and you were among</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
